Guide to the Army Specialized Training Division, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Army Specialized Training Program student transcripts, 1943-1945; Accession 2005-A-117
  - Brenni, Vito Joseph (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Brewer, Jack Dempsey (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Brice, Joseph Anthony (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Bridgman, James Eaglesfiel (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Brill, Andrew (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Brill, Maurice (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Brisendine Robert Harold (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Bristol, Frederick Robert (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Britten, Milton Reese (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Broadbent, Robert Verne (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Brock, Virgil Glenn (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Broderick, John Caruthers (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Brodie, Littleton Mays (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Bronson, Walter Michael Jr (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Brooks, Benjamin Phillips (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Brooks, Richard James (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Brotman, Stanley Seymour (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Brown, Donald Allen (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Brown, Harry Francis Jr (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Brown, Hugh Frazier Jr (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Brown, Nicholas VanVranken (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Brown, Peter Speer (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Brown, William Francis Jr (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Browne, John Henry (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Broyles, Joseph Warren Jr (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Bruhn, Louis George (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Buch, Robert Henry (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Budd, Gerald Gordon (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Bugosh, Andrew (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Burdsal, Alms David (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Burgener, Donald Edward (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Burnham, Robert Jay (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Burns, Bruce Roosevelt (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Burrill, Wilfred Hart (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Buzas, Gabriel Andrew (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Byers, Robert Martin (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Byrum, William Colvig (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Caesar, George Purdy (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Cagle, Harvey Gene (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Cahoon, John Thayer (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Caird, Harry Laurence (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Calabro, Ignazio Vincent (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Callagan, Harry Pierce (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Cameron, William James (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Campbell, Forest Darlyne (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Campbell, Jay Warren (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Canning, George Rolland Jr (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Canning, Thomas Francis III (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Carboni, Omero (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Carman, Carroll Irvin (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Carminati, Dominick Joseph (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Carpenter, Darrell Ward (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Carpenter, Oliver Clinton Jr (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Carpenter, Raymond Leonard Jr (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Carroll, Charles Rivers (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Carroll, Fred Anthony (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Carroll, Holbert Nicholson (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Carry, Charles Albert Jr (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Carstensen William Henry (Box 1, Folder 212 - 213)
  - Carter, Perry Wallace (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Carter, Robert Page (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Carty, Joseph Thomas (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Cascante, Hector Anthony (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Case, Roger Warren (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Casey, Philip Tyler (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - Casnocha, Joseph Aloysius (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - Casper, Ernest John (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - Cassidy, Andrew John (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - Caukin, Robert Kenneth (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - Caulfield, Crandon Edgar (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - Cawley, Arnold Welles (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - Caywood, Gano Dudley (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Cepko, Robert William (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Chabot, Roland Elphege (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - Chandler, Charles Lyon Jr (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Chapman, Leonard Nicholas Jr (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - Chapparro, Michael (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Chmielewski Bernard John (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Chomyk, John (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - Christensen Norman William (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - Christiansen Carroll Stewart (Box 1, Folder 235)
  - Cilley, Franklyn Desmond (Box 1, Folder 236)
  - Clark, John Warren (Box 1, Folder 237)
  - Clark, Lewis Edwin (Box 1, Folder 238)
  - Clark, Sidney Edward (Box 1, Folder 239)
  - Claudio, Alcibiades (Box 1, Folder 240)
  - Clay, Jefferson Leon Jr (Box 1, Folder 241)
  - Clayton, Robert Linwood (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - Clayton, Robert Samuel (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - Clemens, John Charles (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - Cleveland, Charles Ames (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - Clifford, William Dyer (Box 1, Folder 246)
  - Cline, William Edwin (Box 1, Folder 247)
  - Coatsworth James Goulet (Box 1, Folder 248)
  - Cochran, Charles McCann (Box 1, Folder 249)
  - Coen, Edward Arthur (Box 1, Folder 250)
  - Cohen, Harvey David (Box 1, Folder 251)
  - Cohen, Howard Marvin (Box 1, Folder 252)
  - Cohen, Leonard Howard (Box 1, Folder 253)
  - Colbert, Marvin Jay (Box 1, Folder 254)
  - Colburn, Irving Walker (Box 1, Folder 255)
  - Colgate, George Thomas (Box 1, Folder 256)
  - Collins, James Murray (Box 1, Folder 257)
  - Collins, Robert Arthur (Box 1, Folder 258)
  - Collods, Francisco Ortiz (Box 1, Folder 259)
  - Collopy, Walter Francis Xa (Box 1, Folder 260)
  - Comfort, Robert McEwen (Box 1, Folder 261)
  - Commisa, Vincent John (Box 1, Folder 262)
  - Conboy, John Robert (Box 1, Folder 263)
  - Connis, Gerald Ira (Box 1, Folder 264)
  - Connolly, Frank Thomas Jr (Box 1, Folder 265)
  - Connor, John Patrick (Box 1, Folder 266)
  - Conway, Frank Joseph (Box 1, Folder 267)
  - Cooper, Solomon (Box 1, Folder 268)
  - Corbert, Morton (Box 1, Folder 269)
  - Corkery, William Francis (Box 1, Folder 270)
  - Cornelius, Earle Dale Jr (Box 1, Folder 271)
  - Costello, Thomas Anthony (Box 1, Folder 272)
  - Cotter, Frank Edward (Box 1, Folder 273)
  - Coughlin, Richard James (Box 1, Folder 274)
  - Crabb, Ralph Alvin (Box 1, Folder 275)
  - Craine, Thomas Boyce (Box 1, Folder 276)
  - Crandall, Evan Stephen (Box 1, Folder 277)
  - Crane, George Thomas (Box 1, Folder 278)
  - Crank, Charles Edward Jr (Box 1, Folder 279)
  - Cressy, Charles Sumner (Box 1, Folder 280)
  - Crona, Alvin Joseph (Box 1, Folder 281)
  - Cronin, Robert Alan (Box 1, Folder 282)
  - Crowley, Cornelius John (Box 1, Folder 283)
  - Cruickshanks Robert jr (Box 1, Folder 284)
  - Csonka, Steve (Box 1, Folder 285)
  - Cummins, Richard Thomas (Box 1, Folder 286)
  - Cunningham John William (Box 1, Folder 287)
  - Cyr, Lloyd Louis (Box 1, Folder 288)
  - Dabrowski, Mirek John (Box 1, Folder 289)
  - Dahler, Herman William (Box 1, Folder 290)
  - Daignault, Alfred Philip (Box 1, Folder 291)
  - Danielson, Lloyd Clarence (Box 1, Folder 292)
  - Dannebaum, Rex Paul (Box 1, Folder 293)
  - Davenport, William Wyatt (Box 1, Folder 294)
  - Davidson, Donald Lloyd (Box 1, Folder 295)
  - Davis, Linwood (Box 1, Folder 296)
  - Davis, Richard Harris (Box 1, Folder 297)
  - Davis, William Franklin (Box 1, Folder 298)
  - deBruin, James Homer (Box 1, Folder 299)
  - deCastro, Carlos (Box 1, Folder 300)
  - Degen, Jerome (Box 1, Folder 301)
  - Deisher, John Daniel (Box 1, Folder 302)
  - Demain, Stephen (Box 1, Folder 303)
  - Demarest, Daniel Anthony (Box 1, Folder 304)
  - Demetriou, George James (Box 1, Folder 305)
  - DeRosa, Vincent John (Box 1, Folder 306)
  - Desautels, Claude John (Box 1, Folder 307)
  - Dettmann, Vernon Reuben (Box 1, Folder 308)
  - DeVos, George Alphonse (Box 1, Folder 309)
  - Diamond, Irving Mitchell (Box 1, Folder 310)
  - Dick, William Kenneth (Box 1, Folder 311)
  - Dickerson, Charles Henry (Box 1, Folder 312)
  - Dickson, Clinton Edwin (Box 1, Folder 313)
  - Diesing, Paul Robert (Box 1, Folder 314)
  - Dilbarian, Vartkes Richard (Box 1, Folder 315)
  - Dillinger, Charles Kenneth (Box 1, Folder 316)
  - DiMartino, Barbaro (Box 1, Folder 317)
  - Dimin, Lionel Stephan (Box 1, Folder 318)
  - Dines, Charles Henry (Box 1, Folder 319)
  - DiPasquale Philip Joseph (Box 1, Folder 320)
  - Diskind, Meyer Herman (Box 1, Folder 321)
  - Dixon, Francis Edward (Box 1, Folder 322)
  - Dobson, Norman Berry (Box 1, Folder 323)
  - Doherty, James Joseph Cam (Box 1, Folder 324)
  - Dombroff, Sidney (Box 1, Folder 325)
  - Donahue, John Edward (Box 1, Folder 326)
  - Donaldson, Thomas Noyes (Box 1, Folder 327)
  - Donegan, George Joseph (Box 1, Folder 328)
  - Donlon, Edward Joseph (Box 1, Folder 329)
  - Donovan, William Henry (Box 1, Folder 330)
  - Dooley, Wallace Summers (Box 1, Folder 331)
  - Dora, James Edward (Box 1, Folder 332)
  - Dore, Vincent Richard (Box 1, Folder 333)
  - Dorfman, Phillip (Box 1, Folder 334)
  - Dornbush, Milton (Box 1, Folder 335)
  - Dornfest, Herbert (Box 1, Folder 336)
  - Douglas, Charles Thurber (Box 1, Folder 337)
  - Doutre, Alfred Boyd (Box 1, Folder 338)
  - Dowd, Kenneth George (Box 1, Folder 339)
  - Dower, Alfred Francis (Box 1, Folder 340)
  - Dreifuss, Walter (Box 1, Folder 341)
  - Drey, Sylvester Emerson (Box 1, Folder 342)
  - Drinnon, Everett Gostin (Box 1, Folder 343)
  - DuBois, Jack Edwin (Box 1, Folder 344)
  - Duffey, James Donald (Box 1, Folder 345)
  - Duffy, James Albert (Box 1, Folder 346)
  - Duke, Joseph Edward (Box 1, Folder 347)
  - Dunn, Roy Henry (Box 1, Folder 348)
  - Dunton, Rhodes (Box 1, Folder 349)
  - Duros, George John (Box 1, Folder 350)
  - Dutcher, Cornelius Gold (Box 1, Folder 351)
  - Dyck, Harry (Box 1, Folder 352)
  - Dyer, Charles Howard (Box 1, Folder 353)
  - Earley, Clarence Luther (Box 1, Folder 354)
  - Earley, William Leon Jr (Box 1, Folder 355)
  - Earnshaw, Robert Chetwynd (Box 1, Folder 356)
  - Eckert, George Arthur Jr (Box 1, Folder 357)
  - Edelstein, Harvard (Box 1, Folder 358)
  - Edwards, Carlton Lewis (Box 1, Folder 359)
  - Edwards, John Richard (Box 1, Folder 360)
  - Ehrenberg, George (Box 2, Folder 361)
  - Eicher, Robert Theodore (Box 2, Folder 362)
  - Einis, Reuben (Box 2, Folder 363)
  - Eiseman, Cassius Meyer (Box 2, Folder 364)
  - Eisenberg, Jack Solomon (Box 2, Folder 365)
  - Elkanick, Andrew Jr (Box 2, Folder 366)
  - Eller, Burton Harold (Box 2, Folder 367)
  - Elliott, Harold Wardrop (Box 2, Folder 368)
  - Ellis, Kenneth Irving (Box 2, Folder 369)
  - Elson, Milton Ira (Box 2, Folder 370)
  - Emerick, Jack Cecil (Box 2, Folder 371)
  - Eng, Eddie (Box 2, Folder 372)
  - Engel, Robert Earl (Box 2, Folder 373)
  - Engelman, Harold (Box 2, Folder 374)
  - Englis, James Fairfield Jr (Box 2, Folder 375)
  - English, James Fairfield Jr (Box 2, Folder 376)
  - Enquist, Roy John (Box 2, Folder 377)
  - Entes, David Harold (Box 2, Folder 378)
  - Epstein, Israel Eli (Box 2, Folder 379)
  - Ericson, John Edward (Box 2, Folder 380)
  - Etter, Willis Rolland (Box 2, Folder 381)
  - Fabish, John George (Box 2, Folder 382)
  - Facchina, Columbus Ulysses (Box 2, Folder 383)
  - Falk, Leo Joshua Jr (Box 2, Folder 384)
  - Farley, Holt Apgar Jr (Box 2, Folder 385)
  - Farmer, Donald Raymond (Box 2, Folder 386)
  - Faure, John Luciano (Box 2, Folder 387)
  - Faut, Robert Matthew (Box 2, Folder 388)
  - Featherstone Robert Addoms (Box 2, Folder 389)
  - Fein, Alfred Gustave (Box 2, Folder 390)
  - Feinberg, Ira Sheldon (Box 2, Folder 391)
  - Feinsod, Jacques Laurence (Box 2, Folder 392)
  - Feitelberg Edward Sherman (Box 2, Folder 393)
  - Feitelowitz Sidney (Box 2, Folder 394)
  - Feldman, David (Box 2, Folder 395)
  - Fenn, Ormon William (Box 2, Folder 396)
  - Fenstermaker Norman Keith (Box 2, Folder 397)
  - Feraru, Arthur Norman (Box 2, Folder 398)
  - Feroglia, William Eugene (Box 2, Folder 399)
  - Ferree, Grant Russell (Box 2, Folder 400)
  - Ferris, Samuel John (Box 2, Folder 401)
  - Fewkes, William Jesse (Box 2, Folder 402)
  - Fielding, Charles Landry (Box 2, Folder 403)
  - Filmer, Stanley Hewett (Box 2, Folder 404)
  - Fine, Meyer (Box 2, Folder 405)
  - Finigan, Francis Xavier (Box 2, Folder 406)
  - Finkelstein Jerome (Box 2, Folder 407)
  - Finn, Richard Paul (Box 2, Folder 408)
  - Fisher, Herbert Hirsh (Box 2, Folder 409)
  - Fishman, Arnold Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 410)
  - Fitzgerald William Francis (Box 2, Folder 411)
  - Flagg, Donald Elliott (Box 2, Folder 412)
  - Flandreau, Arthur Conover Jr (Box 2, Folder 413)
  - Fleig, Albert Lyn (Box 2, Folder 414)
  - Fleischer, Edward Garner (Box 2, Folder 415)
  - Floreza, Francisco Arsiaga (Box 2, Folder 416)
  - Floyd, Frank Horton Jr (Box 2, Folder 417)
  - Fly, Edwin Clyde (Box 2, Folder 418)
  - Flynn, Frank Michael (Box 2, Folder 419)
  - Flynn, John James (Box 2, Folder 420)
  - Fogelberg, Elwyn Wallace (Box 2, Folder 421)
  - Ford, Kenneth Lewis Jr (Box 2, Folder 422)
  - Ford, Robert Jay (Box 2, Folder 423)
  - Fox, Asher Joseph (Box 2, Folder 424)
  - Fox, John Edward Jos (Box 2, Folder 425)
  - Frank, Robert Burton (Box 2, Folder 426)
  - Frankel, Martin Alexander (Box 2, Folder 427)
  - Fransen, Rene Joseph (Box 2, Folder 428)
  - Frawley, John Gerald (Box 2, Folder 429)
  - Freedman, Gabriel Philip (Box 2, Folder 430)
  - Freedman, Jack Donald (Box 2, Folder 431)
  - Freeman, Murray Sumner (Box 2, Folder 432)
  - Freiwald, Alfred Curran (Box 2, Folder 433)
  - Friedland, Morris (Box 2, Folder 434)
  - Friedman, James Marion (Box 2, Folder 435)
  - Friedman, Marcy Arnold (Box 2, Folder 436)
  - Friedman, Morris (Box 2, Folder 437)
  - Friedrich, Ralph William (Box 2, Folder 438)
  - Friscia, Joseph Domenico (Box 2, Folder 439)
  - Froehlich, Roy Lee (Box 2, Folder 440)
  - Fuldauer, Robert Ralph (Box 2, Folder 441)
  - Fultz, Walter John (Box 2, Folder 442)
  - Gaetke, Edward Otto (Box 2, Folder 443)
  - Gallagher, Arthur Henry (Box 2, Folder 444)
  - Galligan, James Charles (Box 2, Folder 445)
  - Gallo, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 446)
  - Galman, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 447)
  - Gamble, Elmer Walter (Box 2, Folder 448)
  - Gambrell, Carroll Blake Jr (Box 2, Folder 449)
  - Gardiner, Raffi Zaven (Box 2, Folder 450)
  - Gardner, Edgar Everett Jr (Box 2, Folder 451)
  - Gardner, LeRoy Edward (Box 2, Folder 452)
  - Gardner, Oliver Henry (Box 2, Folder 453)
  - Garnier, Gene Edgar (Box 2, Folder 454)
  - Gatzmyer, Stanley Joseph (Box 2, Folder 455)
  - Gault, George William (Box 2, Folder 456)
  - Gelfand, Samuel (Box 2, Folder 457)
  - Georges, Robert William (Box 2, Folder 458)
  - Gerlach, Charles (Box 2, Folder 459)
  - Gerlach, Richard Otto (Box 2, Folder 460)
  - Germain, Melvin (Box 2, Folder 461)
  - Getman, George Herbert (Box 2, Folder 462)
  - Giannarakos George Peter (Box 2, Folder 463)
  - Gibbons, Michael (Box 2, Folder 464)
  - Gidro-Frank Lothar (Box 2, Folder 465)
  - Giesler, Edwin Charles (Box 2, Folder 466)
  - Gilbert, Andrew (Box 2, Folder 467)
  - Gilbert, LeRoy Earl (Box 2, Folder 468)
  - Gilbert, Wallace Carl (Box 2, Folder 469)
  - Gilbertson Robert Lee (Box 2, Folder 470)
  - Gillary, Leo (Box 2, Folder 471)
  - Gilmer, James Hugh (Box 2, Folder 472)
  - Gilmore, Jess Walter Jr (Box 2, Folder 473)
  - Ginsberg, Murray (Box 2, Folder 474)
  - Gitlin, Benjamin (Box 2, Folder 475)
  - Gleason, Robert Everett (Box 2, Folder 476)
  - Glenn, William Anderson (Box 2, Folder 477)
  - Glick, Thomas Jay (Box 2, Folder 478)
  - Glickman, David (Box 2, Folder 479)
  - Glod, Alexander Anthony (Box 2, Folder 480)
  - Goetz, Henry (Box 2, Folder 481)
  - Gojio, George (Box 2, Folder 482)
  - Gold, Max Frank (Box 2, Folder 483)
  - Goldberg, Saul Wilbert (Box 2, Folder 484)
  - Goldberg, Stanley Jack (Box 2, Folder 485)
  - Goldewater Bernard Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 486)
  - Goldman, George David (Box 2, Folder 487)
  - Goldsmith, David Harry (Box 2, Folder 488)
  - Goldworth, Samuel (Box 2, Folder 489)
  - Gookin, James William (Box 2, Folder 490)
  - Gordon, Allan Robert (Box 2, Folder 491)
  - Goudsmit, Alfred (Box 2, Folder 492)
  - Gould, James Wilson (Box 2, Folder 493)
  - Graeff, James Wayne (Box 2, Folder 494)
  - Graff, Miles Weston (Box 2, Folder 495)
  - Graham, Malcolm Euwer (Box 2, Folder 496)
  - Grahl, Robert Louis (Box 2, Folder 497)
  - Grant, Henry (Box 2, Folder 498)
  - Gratiot, Frederick Louis Jr (Box 2, Folder 499)
  - Graw, Philip (Box 2, Folder 500)
  - Greaves, Donald Critchfiel (Box 2, Folder 501)
  - Grebanier, Francis Germinal (Box 2, Folder 502)
  - Green, Thomas Martin III (Box 2, Folder 503)
  - Greenberg, David J (Box 2, Folder 504)
  - Greenberg, Raphael (Box 2, Folder 505)
  - Greeneisen Paul William (Box 2, Folder 506)
  - Greenhouse Ralph (Box 2, Folder 507)
  - Gresher, James Jerome (Box 2, Folder 508)
  - Grieder, Elmer Mori (Box 2, Folder 509)
  - Griffin, Hugh (Box 2, Folder 510)
  - Griffin, Norbert Jerome (Box 2, Folder 511)
  - Griffiths, William Morland (Box 2, Folder 512)
  - Grimberg, Paul Mark (Box 2, Folder 513)
  - Griswold, John Alfred (Box 2, Folder 514)
  - Griswold, Robert Deane (Box 2, Folder 515)
  - Groshong, Dale Vern (Box 2, Folder 516)
  - Grossberg, Harry (Box 2, Folder 517)
  - Gryk, Wesley Casimir (Box 2, Folder 518)
  - Grynberg, Andrew (Box 2, Folder 519)
  - Guild, George P (Box 2, Folder 520)
  - Guilfoile, Joseph Vincent (Box 2, Folder 521)
  - Gulbransen Capron Richardson (Box 2, Folder 522)
  - Gunter, Carl Eugene (Box 2, Folder 523)
  - Haber, Irving (Box 2, Folder 524)
  - Haden, Gene Dale (Box 2, Folder 525)
  - Haibloom, Martin Irving (Box 2, Folder 526)
  - Hall, Alan Keith (Box 2, Folder 527)
  - Hall, John William (Box 2, Folder 528)
  - Halpern, Norman Allen (Box 2, Folder 529)
  - Hamel, Paul Wilfred (Box 2, Folder 530)
  - Hammer, Arthur (Box 2, Folder 531)
  - Hanna, Elmer Joseph (Box 2, Folder 532)
  - Hanson, Richard Carl (Box 2, Folder 533)
  - Harcourt, John Bertram (Box 2, Folder 534)
  - Hark, Louis Francis (Box 2, Folder 535)
  - Harlow, Harold Chadbourne Jr (Box 2, Folder 536)
  - Harper, William Sydney (Box 2, Folder 537)
  - Harrington James Joseph Jr (Box 2, Folder 538)
  - Harrington Paul Lewis (Box 2, Folder 539)
  - Harrington William John (Box 2, Folder 540)
  - Harris, Forest Delbert (Box 2, Folder 541)
  - Harris, Samuel George (Box 2, Folder 542)
  - Harshman, Ira Russell Jr (Box 2, Folder 543)
  - Hart, Hubert Robert (Box 2, Folder 544)
  - Harter, John Joseph (Box 2, Folder 545)
  - Hartley, Joseph Milton Jr (Box 2, Folder 546)
  - Hassett, Robert David (Box 2, Folder 547)
  - Hasty, John Bruner (Box 2, Folder 548)
  - Hatch, Duane Verni (Box 2, Folder 549)
  - Hawkins, Graham Edward Jr (Box 2, Folder 550)
  - Hayes, Herbert Earl (Box 2, Folder 551)
  - Hayes, Thomas Francis (Box 2, Folder 552)
  - Hayes, William Jerome (Box 2, Folder 553)
  - Haynes, Jerome Martin (Box 2, Folder 554)
  - Haynes, John Blake (Box 2, Folder 555)
  - Hazelton, Frank Taber (Box 2, Folder 556)
  - Heavey, John Vincent Jr (Box 2, Folder 557)
  - Hedlund, Fred (Box 2, Folder 558)
  - Hein, Carl Edwin (Box 2, Folder 559)
  - Heintzman, Wilson Clayton (Box 2, Folder 560)
  - Heinz, Edward II (Box 2, Folder 561)
  - Heiss, Charles Gordon (Box 2, Folder 562)
  - Heller, Irving Hellman Jr (Box 2, Folder 563)
  - Heller, Irving Issac (Box 2, Folder 564)
  - Hendry, Frank McGavin (Box 2, Folder 565)
  - Hendry, James Bausch (Box 2, Folder 566)
  - Hennessey, Robert Erwin (Box 2, Folder 567)
  - Herndon, William Irvin (Box 2, Folder 568)
  - Hess, Andrew Joseph (Box 2, Folder 569)
  - Hesse, Siegfried Frank (Box 2, Folder 570)
  - Hetrick, Howard James (Box 2, Folder 571)
  - Heubel, Vincent Francis (Box 2, Folder 572)
  - Hickey, John Gerald (Box 2, Folder 573)
  - Higgins, Richard Thomas (Box 2, Folder 574)
  - Higgins, Roger Rynders (Box 2, Folder 575)
  - Hilbury, Saul (Box 2, Folder 576)
  - Hill, Don Wain (Box 2, Folder 577)
  - Hill, Jack Arnold (Box 2, Folder 578)
  - Hillhouse, Harold Charles (Box 2, Folder 579)
  - Hinderling Ellwood Malcolm (Box 2, Folder 580)
  - Hindin, Allan A (Box 2, Folder 581)
  - Hingst, Lawrence Adolph (Box 2, Folder 582)
  - Hirata, Clinton Likis (Box 2, Folder 583)
  - Hirsch, Elias (Box 2, Folder 584)
  - Hirsch, Warner Michael (Box 2, Folder 585)
  - Hirshtritt Moe (Box 2, Folder 586)
  - Hitchcock, Hugh Wiley (Box 2, Folder 587)
  - Hite, Robert Eugene (Box 2, Folder 588)
  - Hobbs, Kendall Easton (Box 2, Folder 589)
  - Hodgdon, Harold Sheldon Jr (Box 2, Folder 590)
  - Hoffman, Jack Fersner (Box 2, Folder 591)
  - Hoffman, Sigmund (Box 2, Folder 592)
  - Holben, George Edward (Box 2, Folder 593)
  - Holden, William Prescott (Box 2, Folder 594)
  - Holeman, Richard Alvin (Box 2, Folder 595)
  - Hollenbeck Carl Edward (Box 2, Folder 596)
  - Holmes, Lionel Edward (Box 2, Folder 597)
  - Holton, Morris Joseph (Box 2, Folder 598)
  - Holzman, Donald Albert (Box 2, Folder 599)
  - Homer, Clair Reginald (Box 2, Folder 600)
  - Homik, John (Box 2, Folder 601)
  - Honeyman, Alfred Merle (Box 2, Folder 602)
  - Hooley, John Joseph (Box 2, Folder 603)
  - Hopkins, James Edward (Box 2, Folder 604)
  - Horn, John William (Box 2, Folder 605)
  - Horwitz, Solis (Box 2, Folder 606)
  - Houdek, Bernard Richard (Box 2, Folder 607)
  - Howard, Arthur Claud (Box 2, Folder 608)
  - Howard, Gordon Munns (Box 2, Folder 609)
  - Howarth, Thomas William (Box 2, Folder 610)
  - Howell, Ernest Tapper (Box 2, Folder 611)
  - Howell, William Dean (Box 2, Folder 612)
  - Howes, Virgil Monroe (Box 2, Folder 613)
  - Howle, William Palmer (Box 2, Folder 614)
  - Hoyle, Harry Clifford (Box 2, Folder 615)
  - Hoyle, Henry Douglas Jr (Box 2, Folder 616)
  - Hubbard, Charles Appleton (Box 2, Folder 617)
  - Hudak, Stephen Bernard (Box 2, Folder 618)
  - Hughes, David Grattan (Box 2, Folder 619)
  - Hughes, Virgil Emmett (Box 2, Folder 620)
  - Humphreys, Vance Eldon (Box 2, Folder 621)
  - Humphries, Herbert Thomas (Box 2, Folder 622)
  - Hunt, William Harrison M (Box 2, Folder 623)
  - Hunter, Herbert Neal (Box 2, Folder 624)
  - Hurst, John (Box 2, Folder 625)
  - Hurst, martin Lewis (Box 2, Folder 626)
  - Hurt, Wesley Robert Jr (Box 2, Folder 627)
  - Hutchins, Robert Evan (Box 2, Folder 628)
  - Hutchison, Glen Daren (Box 2, Folder 629)
  - Hutton, Jack Withrow (Box 2, Folder 630)
  - Iturbe, Robert Joseph (Box 2, Folder 631)
  - Jacobs, Adrian Gerald (Box 2, Folder 632)
  - Jacobs, Myron Samuel (Box 2, Folder 633)
  - Jaffe, Eugene (Box 2, Folder 634)
  - Jaggar, Scott Hulbert (Box 2, Folder 635)
  - Jakubs, George Aloysius Jr (Box 2, Folder 636)
  - Janison, Bernard Jehovah (Box 2, Folder 637)
  - Jarecki, Edward Henry (Box 2, Folder 638)
  - Jay, Bernard (Box 2, Folder 639)
  - Jenkins, Francis Borgia (Box 2, Folder 640)
  - Jensen, Howard Gram (Box 2, Folder 641)
  - Jensen, Marvin Lee (Box 2, Folder 642)
  - Jerome, Richard Elliot (Box 2, Folder 643)
  - Jew, Kern Jun (Box 2, Folder 644)
  - Johns, Earl Oliver (Box 2, Folder 645)
  - Johnson, James Edward (Box 2, Folder 646)
  - Johnson, Norman Carlyle (Box 2, Folder 647)
  - Johnson, Raymond (Box 2, Folder 648)
  - Johnston, Boyd Brown (Box 2, Folder 649)
  - Johnston, John (Box 2, Folder 650)
  - Johnston, Richard James (Box 2, Folder 651)
  - Jones, Kevan Raymond (Box 2, Folder 652)
  - Jordan, William John (Box 2, Folder 653)
  - Jules, Marcus (Box 2, Folder 654)
  - Kahn, Myron (Box 2, Folder 655)
  - Kahn, Raymond Stanley (Box 2, Folder 656)
  - Kalem, Daniel David (Box 2, Folder 657)
  - Kalinowski Richard John (Box 2, Folder 658)
  - Kaminsky, Jack (Box 2, Folder 659)
  - Kamp, Fred William Jr (Box 2, Folder 660)
  - Kantrowitz Murray (Box 2, Folder 661)
  - Kaplan, Eugene Jason (Box 2, Folder 662)
  - Kappas, Attallah (Box 2, Folder 663)
  - Karafotias Christ (Box 2, Folder 664)
  - Karla, William Joseph (Box 2, Folder 665)
  - Kasoff, Seymour Oscar (Box 2, Folder 666)
  - Kass, Lawrence Norman (Box 2, Folder 667)
  - Kasten, Peter Henry (Box 2, Folder 668)
  - Katwyk, Cornelius Gerrit (Box 2, Folder 669)
  - Katz, Norman (Box 2, Folder 670)
  - Katz, Velvle Arthur (Box 2, Folder 671)
  - Kaufman, Samuel Joseph (Box 2, Folder 672)
  - Kaufman, Harry (Box 2, Folder 673)
  - Kaufmann, Henry William (Box 2, Folder 674)
  - Kavaler, Arthur Raymond (Box 2, Folder 675)
  - Kay, Charles Herbert (Box 2, Folder 676)